healthhub.sg 2017-09-29

# Privacy policy - HealthHub

1\. By providing us with your personal data, you consent to our collection, use, disclosure (including transfer) of your personal data in accordance with this Policy. Please DO NOT provide us with any personal data if your do not accept this Policy.

2\. We may amend this Policy from time to time and will make available the updated Policy on our website at [http://www.healthhub.sg](http://www.healthhub.sg/) (“ **Website** ”). The updated Policy will supercede earlier versions and will apply to personal data provided to us previously. Each time you use our Website or mobile application (“ **App** ”) (collectively referred to as the “ **e-Facilities** ”), or contact, interact or transact with us, you acknowledge and agree that the latest version of this Policy shall apply to you.

3\. We may use "cookies", where a small data file is sent to your browser to store and track information about you when you use our e-Facilities. The cookie is used to track information such as the number of users and their frequency of use, profiles of users and their preferred sites. While this cookie can tell us when you use our e-Facilities and which pages you visit, it cannot read data off your hard disk or mobile device.

4\. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the e-Facilities.

5\. We may collect, use and disclose the personal data received from you for the purposes listed below and any other related or associated purposes (collectively the “ **Purposes** ”):

  1. setting up your account with us and managing your use and access of our e-Facilities; 
  2. managing your relationship with us; 
  3. uploading onto health systems operated and/or initiated by the Government of Singapore, including but not limited to the National Electronic Health Record system managed by the Ministry of Health; 
  4. assisting you with your enquiries; 
  5. obtaining feedback; 
  6. accounting, risk management and record keeping; 
  7. informing you about service upgrades and updates; 
  8. performing network or service enhancement; 
  9. carrying out research, planning and statistical analysis, including satisfaction surveys to improve and personalise our services to you and develop new products and services; 
  10. personalising our services and recommending content related to our services and your health 
  11. offering to you rewards and loyalty programs which you may qualify for; and 
  12. sending you advertisements, information on promotions by our partners or invitations to events. 

6\. If you provide us with personal data:

  1. We may share such personal data with other Government agencies and Public Healthcare Institutions, so as to serve you better, unless such sharing is prohibited by law. 
  2. We will NOT share your personal data with non-Government agencies and non-Public Healthcare Institutions, except where: 
    1. they have been authorised to provide services on behalf of Government agencies or Public Healthcare Institutions;
    2. they are our service providers who provide us with necessary services including but not limited to IT services, hosting and maintenance services, organising of our events, accounting, data analytics services, email messaging services, delivery services, handling of payment transactions, marketing etc;
    3. they are our consultants or professional advisers including but not limited to accountants, lawyers and auditors;
    4. they are authorised users of public health systems operated and/or initiated by the Government of Singapore; or
    5. you have specifically consented to such disclosure.
  3. You consent to us transferring your personal data to any location outside of Singapore for the Purposes set out above. 
  4. d) For your convenience, we may also display to you data you had previously supplied to us or other Government Agencies. This will speed up the transaction and save you from the trouble of repeating previous submissions. Should the data be out-of-date, please supply us with the latest data. 

7\. To safeguard your personal data, all electronic storage and transmission of personal data is secured with appropriate security technologies.

8\. Our e-Facilities may contain links to other websites or applications whose data protection and privacy practices may differ from ours. We are not responsible for the content and privacy practices of these other websites or applications and encourage you to consult the privacy notices of those websites or applications.

9\. Please contact 1800 225 4482 if you :

  1. have any enquires or feedback on our data protection policies and procedures; or 
  2. need more information on or access to data which you have provided to us in the past.
